My name is Alexson.
I'll be your therapist for today.
This is my series on massage therapy.
I am a massage therapist.
I've been studying body work and massage therapy for eight years now.
I went to Englewood School of Massage in Newark, New Jersey, and now, I practice at Paypony Nail and Day Spa.
So we're going to begin today on sports massage.
And sports massage is generally related to athletes, or weekend warriors, or people who kinda like workout, and then they might have problems affiliated with their workout, or maybe joint issues.
Because in this particular massage, there's a lot of movement, there's a lot stretching and there's a lot of passive range of motion that we're going to kinda contribute to the therapeutic part of this massage.
So what we're going to do first is we're going to work on the upper body, and we're going to work on, pretty much, the shoulders and the joints attributed to the shoulders and the arms.